Martin Shelley

FRONT END DEVELOPER

OBJECTIVE

As a dedicated, driven, and highly adaptable Front End Developer, I am passionate about crafting seamless user experiences and possess a strong proficiency in HTML, CSS, Vanilla JS and JavaScript frameworks such as Angular & Vue. I am eager to leverage my expertise in a new, exciting opportunity and contribute to challenging projects that make a difference.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER @ I-NEDA

Sep 2023 - Present

Led on a project for biggest client focusing on the integration of QR code scanning into their applications. Developed numerous customer facing components for various clients using Angular 15+, Typescript & SCSS while meeting project requirements & deadlines. Proactively addressed and resolved bugs, contributing to the overall stability and functionality of multiple client applications.

FRONT END DEVELOPER @ THE WHITE COMPANY

Nov 2021 - Aug 2023

Lead CRO developer at The White Company. Led on a comprehensive testing & personalisation roadmap leveraging HTML, CSS/SCSS & Vanilla JS where one test equated to an £1.8m annual incremental revenue benefit. Acted as main point of contact for technical & non-technical senior stakeholders. Mentoring Junior Front-end developer and overseeing their development.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

IMPLEMENTATION SPECIALIST @ RACING POST

Dec 2018 - Oct 2021

DATA ENGINEER @ LYNCHPIN ANALYTICS

May 2016 - Oct 2018& driven

CONTACT

https://www.linkedin.com/in/martin -shelley-3630a09a/ https://martinshelley.com

ABOUT ME

I am a passionate Front-End Developer with 8 years of experience within Digital, delivering high-impact projects for renowned brands such as Dixons Retail, Ticketmaster, and The White Company from a variety of roles. I love to learn and I am continuously learning new skills, currently Node.js.

I am a keen runner & avid sports fan (particularly NFL).

EDUCATION

Uni of Portsmouth, 2014 BSc(Hons) Computing – 2:1

SKILLS

HTML, CSS/SASS, JS, jQuery Vue.js, Angular 2+, Typescript, Nativescript SQL, Git, Rest APIs, Cypress

OTHER SKILLS

Analytics tools & Tag Management (GA, GTM, Firebase, Adobe Analytics & Adobe Launch) JIRA & Confluence Project & Stakeholder management